It's so beautiful here.
めちゃくちゃ綺麗だよ、ここ
So beautiful.
めちゃ綺麗
Isn't it so beautiful?
めちゃ綺麗じゃない?
So beautiful.
めちゃ綺麗
Right?
でしょ?
After all, it was just running,
やっぱりあれはね、走ってるだけあって、
It's thin.
細いね
I ended up floating on the river.
川の上に浮くなったけどね
Yeah.
うん
fun.
楽しい
Look, there are also chestnuts.
見て、ほら、栗とかもあるもん
amazing.
すごい
I already have legs.
もう脚が
Yeah.
うん
It looks like skin.
肌そう
That's...
それはね...
ah!
ああ!
it hurts!
痛い!
Pappy!
パッパイ!
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Super beautiful!
超綺麗!
this!
これ!
Super beautiful!
超綺麗!
transparent!
透明!
There are naturally beautiful girls out there,
なんか自然と美少女がいるからさ、
This is good, isn't it?
これはいいですよね
amazing!
すごい!
This feels really good though.
めちゃくちゃ気持ちいいんやけどこれ
amazing!
すごい!
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくない?
fun!
楽しい!
Wow!
うー!
Say that.
って言って
The flow is extremely fast.
流れがめちゃくちゃ速い
Wow!
うわ ー!
I'm going to die!
死にます!
Wow!
うわー!
Looks really happy.
めちゃくちゃ嬉しそう
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Looks like it's going to get wet.
濡れそうです
Isn't it bad?
や ばいんじゃないの?
That, that's dangerous.
そっち、そっち危ないって
Is the best one okay?
最高のやつ大丈夫か?
The best one.
最高のやつ
It's really wet though.
めちゃくちゃ濡れてるねんけど
Among them, there are many who are wearing nails.
この中でもネイルつけてるやつもいっぱい
It seems like it's my first time.
初めてやらしい
Among them, as I said earlier.
中でもさ、さっき言ってたけど
Oh amazing.
あーすげー
I'm coming back.
なったねてくる
Ah, amazing.
あーすごい
Come on, Myan-chan, stand up.
さあさあ、ミャンちゃん立ち上がって
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Myan-chan.
ミャンちゃん
Messed up.
めちゃめちゃ
Very close.
めちゃ閉まる